Guide to the Ira Silverberg Papers MSS.110
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Group 3, Series IV: Business/Administration Files
  - Subseries B: Client Projects
    - Client project: The Alphabet Man - Grossman, Richard galley production, 1996-1997 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Client project: Book of Lazarus - Grossman, Richard press kit material, undated (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Client project: Book of Lazarus - Grossman, Richard mailing lists, undated (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Client project: Book of Lazarus - Grossman, Richard book tour, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Client project: Book of Lazarus - Grossman, Richard book tour, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Client project: Book of Lazarus - Grossman, Richard advertisement material, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Client project: Book of Lazarus - Grossman, Richard mailing lists, undated (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Client project: Book of Lazarus - Grossman, Richard press kit material, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Client project: Book of Lazarus - Grossman, Richard internet material, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - Client project: Grossman, Richard - photo, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - Client project: Richard Grossman bios, undated (Box 32, Folder 42)
    - Client project: There Never Was a Rose Without a Thorn - Harryman, Carla, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 43)
    - Client project: Horse Crazy - Gary Indiana - tour info, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 44)
    - Client project: Horse Crazy - Gary Indiana - financial data, testimonials, 1988-1989 (Box 32, Folder 45)
    - Client project: Horse Crazy - Gary Indiana - expenses, 1988-1989 (Box 32, Folder 46)
    - Client project: Horse Crazy - Gary Indiana - book requests, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 47)
    - Client project: Horse Crazy - Gary Indiana - galley mailing, 1988-1989 (Box 32, Folder 48)
    - Client project: First World Ha Ha Ha! - Katzenberger, Elaine, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 49)
    - Client project: Laure: The Collected Writings press releases, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 50)
    - Client project: The Lotus Crew - Stewart Meyer, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 51)
    - Client project: Where Every Breath is a Prayer - Ortner, John book tour info, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 52)
    - Client project: Where Every Breath is a Prayer and Eros mailing info, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 53)
    - Client project: Against Empire - Parenti, Michael, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 54)
    - Client project: Mind Grenades - Plunkett, John and Rossetto, Louis, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 55)
    - Client project: The Heart's Desire - Rachlin, Nahid, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 56)
    - Client project: Head Shots - Rosenberg, Aura / Indiana, Gary / Tillmann, Lynne - tear sheets, articles, correspondence, mailing lists, 1995-1996 (Box 32, Folder 57)
    - Client project: Allan Stein - Stadler, Matthew publishing agreement, July, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 58)
    - Client project: The Post-Therapeutic Memoir - Stone, Laurie publishing agreement, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 59)
    - Client project: Nearly Roadkill - Sullivan, Caitlin and Bornstein, Kate, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 60)
    - Client project: Dead Jackie Susann Quarterly 2, April, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 61)
    - Client project: Valley of the Dolls - Susann, Jacqueline publicity, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 62)
    - Client project: A Conversation with Jonathan Coe - Taylor, Charles, March, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 63)
    - Client project: Bayamus and Cardinal Polotuo - Themerson, Stephan, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 64)
    - Client project: Nice Boy - press release - Veltri, George, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 65)
    - Client project: Returning to "A", 1995 (Box 32, Folder 66)
    - Client project: "A" Warhol, Andy contracts, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 67)
    - Client project: The Death and Letters of Alice James - Yeazell, Ruth, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 68)
  - Subseries C: Financial Files
    - Burroughs Communication - financial, 1995-1996 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - City Lights - Financial, 1995-1996 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Coach House Press - financial, 1995-1996 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Corporate taxes, undated (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Credit card statements, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Credit card statements, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - D.A.P. - financial, 1995-1996 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - The Drawing Center - financial, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Exact Change - financial, 1995-1996 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Financial, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Financial, 1987-1989 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Financial, 1987-1989 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Financial, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Financial, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Financial, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Financial, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Financial, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Financial, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Financial, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Financial, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Financial, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Financial, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Financial, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Financial, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Financial, 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Financial, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Financial, 1991-1992 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Financial, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Financial, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Financial, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Financial, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Financial, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Financial, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Financial, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Financial, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Financial, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Financial, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - Financial, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - Financial, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Financial, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - Financial, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - Financial, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Financial, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Financial, March 1995 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Financial, March, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Financial, January, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Financial, 1994-1995 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Financial, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Financial, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Financial, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Financial, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Financial, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Financial, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Financial, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Financial, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Financial, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Financial, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - I.S.C. Adminstrative, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - I.S.C. A T and T statements, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - I.S.C. Chase Bank statements, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1994-1995 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 37)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 38)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 39)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 40)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 41)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 42)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - I.S.C. financial, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Kodansha America - financial, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Payroll - I.S.C., 1995 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - RE/SEARCH financial, 1995-1996 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Royalties, 1990-2002 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Royalties, 1991-1998 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Royalties, 1992-1998 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Royalties, 1992-1998 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Royalties, 1994-1998 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Royalties, 1994-1998 (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Royalties, 1994-2000 (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - Royalties, 1995-2000 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - Royalties, 1995-2001 (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - Royalties, 1996-2001 (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - Royalties, 1998-2004 (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - Royalties, 1999-2005 (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - Royalties, 2000-2004 (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - Royalties, 2001-2005 (Box 38, Folder 36)
    - Royalties, 2002-2005 (Box 38, Folder 37)
    - Serpent's Tail - financial, 1995-1996 (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - Solicitations (credit cards and bills), 1995 (Box 38, Folder 39)
    - Thunder's Mouth Press - financial, 1995-1996 (Box 38, Folder 40)
    - Turtle Point Press - financial, 1995-1996 (Box 38, Folder 41)
  - Subseries D: Tear Sheets, Reviews and Clippings
    - Kathy Acker - articles, testimonials, 1983-1985 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Don Quixote - Kathy Acker tear sheets and reviews, 1985-1987 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Don Quixote - Kathy Acker reviews and articles, 1986-1987 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Literal Madness - Kathy Acker reviews, 1987-1988 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Tear sheets - Kathy Acker, 1987-1989 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Kathy Acker obituaries, December 1997 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Reviews, tear sheets - The Ancient Ones, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Reviews, tear sheets - A.R.T. Press, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Reviews, tear sheets - Chet Baker, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Reviews, tear sheets - Martine Barrat, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Reviews, tear sheets - Joseph Beuys, 1990-1991 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Reviews, tear sheets - Black Art, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Reviews, tear sheets - Paul Bowles, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Reviews, tear sheets - Rene Burri, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Everything is Permitted tear sheets (Burroughs), 1992 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - City Lights articles, releases, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - City Lights articles, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Reviews, tear sheets - Larry Clark, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Reviews, tear sheets - Chuck Close, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Coach House Press book reviews, tear sheets, 1993-1994 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Coin Locker Babies - Ryu Murakami tear sheets, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - L.A. Weekly articles on Dennis Cooper, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Closer - Dennis Cooper reviews, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Curbstone Press articles and cover proofs, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - DeAgostini tear sheets, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Reviews, tear sheets - DKNY NYC, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Reviews, tear sheets - Arthur Elgort's model manual, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Exact Change Press clippings, 1992-1993 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Reviews, tear sheets - Fluxus, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - Reviews, tear sheets - Robert Frank, 1987-1994 (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - Reviews, tear sheets - Klaus Franke, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 31)
    - Reviews, tear sheets - Lee Friedlander, 1993-1994 (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - Reviews, tear sheets - Henry Geldzahler, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - Allen Ginsburg obituary material, April 1997 (Box 39, Folder 34)
    - Article re Margery Kempe (Robert Gluck) in The Nation, May, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 35)
    - Reviews, tear sheets - Nan Goldin, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 36)
    - Tear sheets: A Double Life - Goldin, Nan and Armstrong, David, 1994-1995 (Box 39, Folder 37)
    - The Alphabet Man - Grossman, Richard clippings, tear sheets, 1993-1994 (Box 39, Folder 38)
    - Book of Lazarus - Grossman, Richard blurbs, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 39)
    - Grossman, Richard tear sheets, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 40)
    - Reviews, tear sheets: Kim Harlow, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 41)
    - Reviews, tear sheets: Dave Hickey, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 42)
    - Book reviews, tear sheets (High Risk), 1990-1994 (Box 39, Folder 43)
    - High Risk - reviews and tear sheets, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 44)
    - High Risk 2 - reviews, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 45)
    - Horse Crazy - Gary Indiana reviews, articles, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 46)
    - Reviews, tear sheets - Jess: a Grand Collage, 1993-1994 (Box 39, Folder 47)
    - Reviews, tear sheets - Donald Judd, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 48)
    - The Other Side of Heaven - Karlin, Thai, Khue articles and reviews, 1995-1996 (Box 39, Folder 49)
    - Reviews, tear sheets, press releases - Evelyn Lau, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 50)
    - Reviews, tear sheets - Susan Lipper, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 51)
    - Reviews, tear sheets - Vitas Luckus, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 52)
    - Reviews, tear sheets - Mark Mack, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 53)
    - Reviews, tear sheets - Fred Mayer, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 54)
    - Cookie Mueller article, undated (Box 39, Folder 55)
    - Reviews, tear sheets - Mario Cravo Neto, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 56)
    - Reviews, tear sheets - Dino Pedriali, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 57)
    - Reviews, tear sheets - Poet and Pilot, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 58)
    - Reviews, tear sheets - Edward Quinn, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 59)
    - Serpent's Tail database info and clippings, 1995-1996 (Box 39, Folder 60)
    - Ira Silverberg articles and tearsheets, 1990-1999 (Box 39, Folder 61)
    - Ira Silverberg articles, April,k 1997 - October, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 62)
    - Reviews, tear sheets - Matin A. Sugarman, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Reviews, tear sheets - Pahi Sowalsky and Judith Swirsky, 1993-1994 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Valley of the Dolls - Susann, Jacquelin tear sheets, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Valley of the Dolls - Susann, Jacquelin articles, catalogs, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Tear sheets, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Tear sheets, 1988-1990 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Tear sheets, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Tear sheets, articles, 1992-1995 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Tear sheets, articles, 1993-1994 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Tear sheets, articles, 1993-1994 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Tear sheets, 1993-1996 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Tear sheets, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Tear sheets, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Tear sheets, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Tear sheets, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Tear sheets, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Tear sheets, 1994-1996 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Tear sheets, articles, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Tear sheets, press releases, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Tear sheets, press releases, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Tear sheets, press releases, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Tear sheets, reviews, 1995-1996 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Tear sheets, 1996-1997 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Tear sheets, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Tear sheets, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Tear sheets, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Tear sheets, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - Various articles, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Various articles, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Various press materials (Time, Lilith) and photos, 1994-1997 (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - Various tear sheets, reviews, April, 1997 - August, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - Various tear sheets, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 32)
    - The Velvet Years - Tillman, Lynne. Thunder Mouth Press. Tear sheets, publicity, 1995-1996 (Box 40, Folder 33)
    - Reviews, tear sheets: James Turrell, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 34)
    - Reviews, tear sheets: Andy Warhol, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 35)
    - Reviews, tear sheets: Western Artists, African Art, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 36)
    - Young Men's Institute - article, 2000-2001 (Box 40, Folder 37)
- Group 3, Series V: Personal Files
  - AIDS as Apocalypse, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Academic Transcripts, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Apartment lease - Ira Silverberg, 1988-1999 (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - Apfelschnitt benefit, February 1990 (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - Byron related material, 1992-2002 (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - Byron veterinarian bills, May, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - Cards: birthday, New Years, etc, 1988-1990 (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - Cards: birthday, New Years, etc, 1992-1993 (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - Christmas cards, 1998-2002 (Box 40, Folder 46)
  - Datebook, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 47)
  - Datebook inserts, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 48)
  - Datebook, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 49)
  - Daily planner, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 50)
  - Daily planner, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Daily planner, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Datebook, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Evangelical ephemera, undated (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Financial (personal), 1991 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Financial (personal), 1991 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Financial (personal), 1992 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Allen Ginsburg, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Invitation to Ginsburg poetry reading, July, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Giorno Poetry Systems - AIDS donations, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Heterosexual Behaviour in the Age of AID, undated (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - High School diploma, June, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Ikea Interplan, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Invitations, 1984-1994 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Invitations - Grauerholz, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Invitations etc., 1984-1988 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Lease, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Lost child poster, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Medical, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Medical / Pharmaceutical, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Memorial Info: Silverberg, Abe; Kolovakos, Gregory and Apfelscnitt, Carl, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Misc flyers and documents, 1979-1987 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Cookie Mueller photo, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Obituaries - Cookie Mueller, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - National Book Awards, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - NYPD, undated (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Personal Finances, undated (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Photographs - Kathy Acker, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Untitled photos - Carl Apfelschnitt, undated (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Photographs (Byron), undated (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Photos: Cooper, Dennis, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Family photographs, 1993, undated (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Photographs: Fire Island, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Photos: Dan Green, Lord Weidenfeld, John Herman, untitled (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Photographs: London, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - Photo: Massimo, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 41, Folder 42)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 41, Folder 43)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 41, Folder 44)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 41, Folder 45)